New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Files 6202
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Meeting Files, 5/22/96-4/26/98. (Box 10)
  - School to Work Opportunities Adv. Council, Renaissance Mayflower, 1127 Conn. Ave NW, Washington, D.C., 1997 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Dec 1- 2
  - NSSB Washington D.C., 1997 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Workforce Development System Steering Committee, Albany, NY, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Dec 23, 1:30 pm
  - NEA NY Board of Directors Embassy Suites, Syracuse, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Jan 9, 9pm
  - Northeast council AFL-CIO Caribe Hilton, San Juan, PR, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Jan 15-20
  - New York City School to Work Institute, business & Labor Panel, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Jan 21-23
  - NSSB Executive Committee Mtg. @ NSSB Office Washington D.C., 1998 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    Jan 21
  - NYC School to Work Inst. New York Hilton Hotel, NYC, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Jan 21, 4pm
  - AFT/NEA Talks, Hyatt Regency Washington, 400 NJ Ave., NW Regency A Ballroom Level, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    Jan 24, 12pm
  - NSSB Sheraton Washington Hotel, Washington D.C., 1998 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    Jan 27
  - Workers' comp Navigator Mtg. Mt. Sinai Medical Center, 110 E 101st Street, NYC, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    Jan 29, 11am
  - Irish-American Labor Coalition Sheraton New York Hotel & Tower New York, NY, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    Jan 30, 6pm
  - Senate Breakfast LOB Rm 711, Albany, NY, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    Feb 3, 8am
  - AFT Executive Council, Fontaine Bleau Hilton Resort Miami Beach, FL, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    Feb 8-10 1 of 2
  - AFT Executive Council, Fontaine Bleau Hilton Resort Miami Beach, FL, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    Feb 8-10 2 of 2
  - Jobs for the Future Job Mtg. Hampshire House 84 Beacon Boston, MA, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    Feb 9-10, 12 pm
  - National Institute for Literature 800 Connecticut Avenue, NW Suite 200, Washington, D.C., 1998 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    Feb 12, 9 am
  - Education International, Hotel New Siru, Place Rogierl, Brussels, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    Feb 25-26
  - NSSB Board Meeting Omni Shoreman Hotel, 2500 Calvert Street, NW Washington 20008, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    Feb 19-20
  - NYS School-to-Work Advisory Council, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    Mar 18
  - NACFAM's Annual Conference Omni Shoreham, Washington, D.C., 1998 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    Mar 25
  - Cornell Board of Trustees, Ithaca, NY, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    Mar 26-28
  - NYS AFL-CIO Industrial Div. Conference, Clarion Hotel, NF, NY, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    Mar 27-29
  - NCUIP Legislative Cocktail Party Best Western, Lockport, NY, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    Mar 27, 4pm
  - AFT Vocational Education Task Force Washington Court, Washington, DC, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    April 2-5
  - STW Adv. Council Meeting Business council, 12 Corporate Woods Albany, NY, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    April 6 1pm
  - Cornell University ILR Bldg. Dedication Week, Cornell University Room - Statler Hotel, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    April 16-18
  - NSSB Committee Meetings, Ritz-Carlton Pentagon City, 1250 S Hayes Street Arlington VA, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    April 22, 9am
  - PSRP Conference Washington Hilton Hotel, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    April 24-26
- Meeting Files, 4/29/98-10/19/98. (Box 11)
  - Westchester Education Coal. Conference, Performing Arts Ctr, Purchase College, NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - NYSUT's RA Sheraton Towers, NYC, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Northeast Public Employee Conference Bally's Park Place, Atlantic City, NJ, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    May 3-5
  - NSSB Executive committee Meeting Corning Inc. 717 5th Avenue 2nd Floor, New York City, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    May 5, 10am
  - School-to-Work Coordinators Desmond Hotel, Albany, NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    May 5-6
  - Lower Hudson Regional Education Conference, Hotel Thayer, West Point, NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    May 7, 3:30pm
  - NY Labor History Assoc. Annual Labor History Conference, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    May 9
  - The Women's Venture Fund, Inc. Columbia University, Int'l Affairs Bldg. 15th Floor, 420 W 118th Street, New York, NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    May 14
  - Center for Career Development Nat'l Advisory Board of Gov. PA McKernan Hosp Ct., So. Maine Technical college, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    June 1-2
  - NSSB Board Meeting Ritz Carlton Pentagon City Arlington, VA, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    May 27-29
  - National Board for Professional Teaching Standards Hyatt Regency hotel, Reston, VA, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    June 5-7
  - Jobs for the Future Board Meetings Hampshire House, Boston, MA, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    June 9 9am
  - NYS Dept. of Health Conference Protecting the Workers of NY Omni Hotel Albany, NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    June 10, 2 pm
  - J Flaherty Retire Dinner Boston Park Plaza Hotel Boston, MA, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    June 13
  - Northeast council AFL-CIO Meeting Grand Hotel, Cape May, NJ, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    June 15-18
  - VICA's Nat'l Leadership and Skills Conference, Kansas City, MO, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    June 23-25
  - Exhibit at Wagner Labor Arch. 70 Square South, 10th Floor New York, NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    July 2, 10am
  - NYS STW Adv. Council Sustain-ability Comm., NYSAC Conf. Rm 111 Pine Street, Albany, NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    July 9, 10:30am
  - US Euro Net, Denver, CO, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    July 11-16
  - AFT Convention, New Orleans Hilton Riverside, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    July 14-22
  - AFT Convention, New Orleans Hilton Riverside, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - NYS Congressional Delegation Breakfast, Rayburn Office Bldg. Room 2105, Washington D.C., 1998 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    July 23, 8am
  - Education International World Congress, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    July 24-28
  - US Dept. of Labor, UI Dialogue Marriott, 85 West Street, Salon A. 3rd Floor, NYC, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    Aug 6 10am
  - NYS STW Sustainability Comm. NYATEP Office - 3rd Floor, conf. Rm 111 Pine Street, Albany, NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    Aug 21, 10:30am
  - Meeting with Joe Welch Albany Office, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    Sept 9, 9:30am
  - NSSB Executive Committee NSSB, 1441 L Street, NW, #9000 Washington, D.C., 1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    Sept 10, 10am
  - Fiscal Policy think Tank Our NYC Office, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Sept 11, 11:30am
  - NYC CLC Reception @ City Hall Rotunda, NYC, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    Sept 11, 5 pm
  - Union Square Park Designated as a National Historic Landmark, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    Sept 12, 9 am
  - Putnam County Democratic Party Dinner, Sheet Metal Workers Union Hall Southeast (Brewster), NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    Sept 12, 7:30pm
  - Annual Labor Mass, St. Patrick's Cathedral, New York City, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    Sept 13, 10:15am
  - Dan Frasca Meeting, NYSUT, 159 Wolf Road, Albany, NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    Sept 16, 3pm
  - Tri-County United Way Kickoff Luncheon, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    Sept 23
  - School-to-Work Advisory Cnl. The Business Cnl., 12 Corp. woods, Albany, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    Sept 24, 10 am
  - TV 8, 63 Quaker Road, Queensbury, NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    Sept 23, 2pm
  - Skill and Workplace Change: Labor's Stake in Skill Standards Workshop Machinists' Lodge, Seattle, WA, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    Sept 30
  - NYS Labor Religion Coalition Press Conference on Child Labor State University Uptown Campus, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    Oct 7, 11am
  - NYS STW Sustainability Comm. Meeting, 111 Pine Street, 3rd Floor, Albany, NY, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    Oct 7, 9am
  - Strengthening the Use of Skill Stand. Through Partnerships, Doubletree Hotel, Seattle Airport, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    Sept 28, 9am
  - Jobs for the Future 88 Broad St. 8th Floor, Boston, MA, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    Oct 13, 9am
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting, Washington hilton hotel, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    Oct 13-14 1 of 2
  - AFT Executive council Meeting Washington Hilton Hotel, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    Oct 13-14 2 of 2
  - Meeting with Ellen Scully & David Wilcox, Washington, DC, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    Oct 14
  - NE AFL-CIO Council, Samoset Resort, MA, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    Oct 15-17
  - NSSB Labor Caucus Meeting AFL-CIO Headquarters, Room 805 Washington, D.C., 1998 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Meeting Files, 10/21/98-4/24/99. (Box 12)
  - NYS Office of the Aging, Here, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Oct 21, 1:30pm
  - Workforce Investment Act Meeting w/ Comm. McGowan, 345 Hudson Street New York City, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Oct 22, 12pm
  - Cornell University Board of Directors, Ithaca, New York, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Oct 21-24
  - SED Symposium, Century Inn, Latham, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Nov 2, 9:30am
  - School-to-Work Advisory Comm. Employer Labor Comm MT Teleconference Sheraton Saratoga Springs Hotel, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Nov 5, 2pm
  - NBPTS, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Nov 7-8
  - AFT & Labor's Stake in 21st Century International Affairs Seminar Washington D.C., 1998 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Nov 18-19
  - AFT Voc Ed Task Force Meeting Wyndam hotel, Miami, FL, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Nov 19-22
  - NSSB Executive Committee Meeting Corning's NY City Office, 717 Fifth Ave., 2nd Floor, New York, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Adv. Cnl for School-to-Work Oppor. Renaissance Mayflower Hotel, 1127 Connecticut Ave., NW., Washington D.C., 1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Nov 23-24
  - National Institute for Literature Equipped for the Future, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Dec 1, 9:30am
  - State Federation Officers' Conference, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Dec 3-4
  - NSSB Hotel Washington, Washington, D.C., 1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Dec 10
  - WIA Town Hall Meeting Marriott Hotel Downtown, NYC, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - National Summit on 21st Century Skills for 21st Century Jobs Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Jan 12
  - Gov. Task Force on Independent Contractors, Office of the State Insurance Fund,15 Computer Drive West, Albany`, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Jan 13
  - Condado Plaza Hotel San Juan, PR, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Jan 14
  - NSSB Committee Meetings @ NSSB Boardroom, 1441 L St., NW Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Jan 20, 8:30am
  - NSSB Executive Committee Mtg. NSSB, 1441 S St., NW Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - National Skill Standards Board Executive Committee Meeting NSSB Office, Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - STW Sustainability Comm Mtg. 111 Pine St. Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Jan 22, 10:30am
  - NYS STW Advisory Council Mtg. Business Council, 12 Corporate Woods, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    Jan 28, 10am
  - Tanner dinner, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    Jan 29
  - Cornell Board of Trustees Weill Medical college of Cornell University, 1300 York Avenue, NYC, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    Jan 29-30
  - Task Force on Independent Contractors Hearings, Hearing Room A, LOB, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - NSSB Mtg. w/ Ray Bramucci DOL 200 Constitution Ave Washington, D.C. RMS 2307, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - 270 Broadway, Room 2400 New York City TFIC Hearing, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    Feb 4, 10am
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting Wyndham Resort Miami Beach, FL, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    Feb 7-10
  - NSSB Retreat, Landowner Conf. Resort, 44050 Woodridge Pkwy. Leesburg, VA 20176, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    Feb 18-19
  - NSSB Retreat, Landsdowne conf. Resort, 44050 Woodridge Pkwy, Leesburg, VA 20176, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Progress Report, Hospitality and Tourism Skill Standards council NSSB Meeting, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    Feb 9
  - NSSB Meeting w/ Bruce Herman Washington, D>C., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    Feb 22, 2pm
  - Coalition of MTA Employee Unions Transportation Legis. Conference, Empire State Plz Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    Feb 23-24
  - Task Force on Indp. Contractors Hearings, Mahoney St Off Bldg 65 Court Street, Buffalo, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    Feb 25, 10 am
  - Meeting w/ Assem. Canastrari Assembly Chamber, 3rd Floor CAP, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    March 1, 2pm
  - Governor's task Force on Independent Contractors Mtg. Stte insurance Fund Bldg., 1 Watervliet Avenue, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    Mar 10, 11am
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Ithaca, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    Mar 11-12
  - School-to-Work Institute, Sheraton Inn Airport, Walden Avenue & I90 Thruway, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    Mar 15, 8am
  - LCS Meeting, 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    Mar 24, 12pm
  - NYS AFL-CIO Legislative Conf. NYS Museum, Clarke Auditorium Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    Mar 24, 2pm
  - Workers' Comp Training Prog. Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - NSSB Executive Committee & Committee Meetings, NSSB Boardroom, 1441 L St., NW Suite 9000, Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    Mar 15
  - Press Conference "Day of Action" LCA Press Room, LOB, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    Mar 30, 1pm
  - 1999 Judge William B. Groat Alumni Award (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - NYSUT RA Niagara Falls, NY, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    April 22-24
- Meeting Files, 4/27/99-11/16-99. (Box 13)
  - NSSB Conference Call, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    April 27, 11am
  - May Day Party, Troy's Riverspark Visitor Center, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    April 30, 7pm
  - AFL-CIO Ex Cnl Comm on Union Education & Training, Sagamore Hill room, Washington Court Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    May 5, 7:30am
  - Nat'l Asses. Of Voc Ed Indep Adv Panel., US Dept of Educ., 400 Maryland Ave SW Barnard Auditorium, Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    May 6-7
  - Northeast Public Employee Conference, Bally's Park Place Atlantic City, NJ, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    May 11-13
  - NYS AFL-CIO Community Services Agency Conference, Bally's Park Place, Atlantic City, NJ, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    May 12-14
  - NSSB Board Meeting [folder 1 of 2], 1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    May 17-18
  - NSSB Board Meeting [folder 2 of 2], 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    May 17-19
  - AFT Executive Council, Omni Shoreham Hotel, Blue Room, Washington, D.C., 1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    May 18, 1:30 pm
  - NYS STW Sustainability Comm Mtg., NYATEP, 111 Pine Street Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    May 19, 3pm
  - NYS STW Adv. Comm. Mtg. Business Council, Corporate Woods, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    May 20, 10am
  - PEF Contract Rally, Building 5 Vendor Area, State Campus, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    May 20, 12pm
  - Cornell Univ. Board of Trustees, Graduation Weekend, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    May 21-24 1of 2
  - Cornell Univ. Board of Trustees, Graduation Weekend, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    May 21-24 2 of 2
  - NBPTS, Hyatt Dulles, @ airport, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    May 22-23
  - NYSUT Committee of 100 Desmond Hotel, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - AFT Executive Council Mtg. Omni Shoreham Hotel 2500 Calvert Street, NW Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    May 25, 9:30am
  - Public Hearing on Workforce Investment Act, Hamilton Hearing Room B, LOB, 2nd Fl., Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    May 25, 11am
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Cornell Univer., Ithaca, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - National Institute for Literacy 800 Connecticut Avenue, NW Suite 200, conference Room, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    June 2, 9a-5p
  - Pension Task Force Meeting 125 Barclay St DC 37, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    June 4, 2:30pm
  - Ctr. For Career Development So. Maine Tech College, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    June 7, 9am
  - JFF, Seaport Hotel, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    June 7-8, 5pm
  - Unity Meeting, Albany Office, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    June 9, 2pm
  - Working For America Inst., National Conference, Las Vegas, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    June 12-15
  - Right to Organize, IBT Lo. 317 Union Hall, 566 Spencer Street, Syracuse, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    June 24
  - 11am OPEIU, 1pm Sheraton New York, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    July 1
  - NEA Representative Assembly Peabody Orlando Hotel, 9801 International Drive, Orlando Florida, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    July 2-6
  - AFT Quest, Hilton Washington, 1919 CT, NW, Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    July 7-11
  - JETT Con '99, Hilton Wash & Towers Washington D.C., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    July 14-16
  - Our Congressional Breakfast B369 Rayburn HOB, Washington Cruise 5:30pm, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    July 15
  - NSSB Committee Meetings & Board Meeting, NSSB Boardroom 1441 L Street, NW, Suite 900 Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    July 20, 9:30a-8:30p
  - Special Olympics Golf Classic Oak Hill Country Club Rochester, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    Aug 2, 8:30am
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council Omni Hotel, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    Aug 12-14
  - DSCC Annual Golf Day Willow Ridge Country Club 123 N. Street, Harrison, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    Aug 16, 10:30am
  - NSSB Executive Committee Mtg. @NSSB, 1441 L Street, Wash. D.C., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    Sept 9, 10am
  - NYC (Box 13, Folder 37)
    Sept 15
  - Kate Mullaney Gravesite St. Peters Cemetery, Oakwood Avenue, Troy, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Sept 18, 11am
  - NYS Capital Labor Parade Meet N. Main & Washington Ave Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    Sept 25
  - JFF-NYC (Box 13, Folder 40)
    Sept 21
  - Cardinals Comm of the Laity Hospitality & Tourism Div. Award Dinner-dance, Sheraton NY Hotel & Towers, NYC, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    Sept 22, 7pm
  - Labor Coordination Reg. conf. Syracuse, New York, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    Sept 23, 10am
  - US Army War College Class of Symposium 2000, NYC Office, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    Sept 24, 10am
  - Video Taping in NYC Office, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    Sept 27
  - Information Systems Mtg. w Consortium for Worker Educ. 90 State Street, Suite 601 Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    Sept 28, 11am
  - Labor Council Meeting, 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    Sept 29, 10am
  - NSSB Board Meeting, Mississippi Isle of Capri, Biloxi, MS, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    Sept 29-Oct 1
  - NSSB, Hilton (Washington Dulles Airport), 1999 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - AFT Executive council Meeting Hyatt Regency Washington, Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    Oct 4, 7pm
  - Meeting with Jim Dillon Building 12, room 592, State Campus, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    Oct 6, 12:30pm
  - AFL-CIO Mtgs. California, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    Oct
  - Jobs for the Future Boston, MA, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Chautauqua Conf on Regionalism & education, Chautauqua Inst., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    Oct 27-29
  - Mtg. w/ com. McGowan, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    Nov 4, 2p
  - National Assessment of Voc. Ed., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    Nov 15-16
- Meeting Files, 11/18/99-4/5/00. (Box 14)
  - NYSUT RA, NY Hilton Hotel New York, NY, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    April 6-8
  - NSSB Committee Meetings, 1441 L Street Suite 9000 Washington D.C., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    April 12, 8am, 7:15pm Executive Session Dinner
  - Advisory Panel for Career and Technical Education, Marriott Hotel Wolf road, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    April 18, 10am
  - NSSB Washington D.C., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - National Research Center for Career & Technical Education Advisory Council Assoc. for Career & Technical Ed., 1410 King Street, Alexandria, VA 22314, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    April 12, 9a-3:30p
  - Conference Call with Nancy Mills, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    April 24, 11:30am
  - Organizing Meeting, Albany Labor Temple, 890 third street Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    April 26, 10 am
  - workers comp LMC, Cornell University, Room 120 Conference Center, Ithaca, NY, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    April 27, 9:30 am
  - Hudson-Mohawk Labor Fest. 2000 Cohoes Music Hall Cohoes, NY (Box 14, Folder 9)
    May 1, 6:30-9:30pm
  - Fiscal Policy Institute Board Mtg., Rm. 104-A, LOB, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    May 3, 12:30pm 1 of 2
  - Fiscal Policy Institute Board Mtg., Rm. 104-A, LOB, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    May 3 12:30pm 2 of 2
  - Ellis Island Medals of Honor Awards Gala, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    May 6
  - Ellis Island Medals of Honor Awards Gala, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    May 6 2 of 2
  - NSSB Labor Caucus Conference Call, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    May 8 11am
  - Pension Fairness Rally East Capital Park, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    May 9, 12:30pm
  - Advisory Panel for Career & Technical Education, Marriott Hotel, Wolf Road, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    May 11, 10am
  - Federal Judicial Conference Sheraton New York & Towers, NYC, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    May 11, 3pm
  - Working for America Institute Waldorf Astoria Hilton, New York City, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    May 13-16
  - NY Parks & Conservation Assoc. Reception honoring Paul Bray, Ft. Orange Club Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    May 16, 6pm
  - AFT Executive Council, Hotel Washington, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - AFT Executive Council, Hotel Washington, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - New Alliance Kick-Off Sheraton New York & Towers New York City, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    May 19, 9:30am
  - NSSB Board Meeting, Holiday Inn Select, 480 King St Old Towne Alexandria, VA, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    May 16-17
  - NSSB Board Meeting, Holiday Inn Select, 480 King St. Old Towne Alexandria, VA, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    May 16-17, 2 of 2
  - LMC Meeting, Workers' Compensation Board, Albany, NY, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    May 18
  - ESAC 2000: Crossing The Millennium 56th Annual Eastern Seaboard Apprenticeship conference, Rye town Hilton, Rye Brook, NY (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - National Institute for Literacy 1775 I Street NW, Suite 730 Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    May 23, 9am
  - CWA Unfair Labor Practice Protest Strike Federal Hall (across fr. NYSE) NYC, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    May 24, 11am
  - Cornell University Trustee Meeting, Ithaca, New York, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    May 26-27
  - ILO Conference, Geneva, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    May 29-June 10
  - State School-to-Work Directors & School-to-Work National Advisory Council, Washington Court Hotel Capitol Hill, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    May 31-June 1
  - 46th Annual National Security Seminar, US Army War College Arlisle, Barracks, PA, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    June 5-9
  - Int'l Adv. Bd. Of Governors Center for Career Development So. Maine technical college, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    June 5-6
  - Jobs for the Future Boston, MA, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    June 12, 3pm
  - National Design Group, New Design for Career & Technical Education at Secondary and Postsecondary Levels, Radisson Hotel, 615 Washington Avenue, SE, Minneapolis, MN, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    June 15-16
  - The Right to Organize!, Stedman Room, Colonie Town Library, 629 Albany shaker, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    June 15
  - Labor educators Forum, SEIU 32B/J, 101 Avenue of the Americas, NYC, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    June 19, 10am
  - The Working Theatre, West Bank Caf, 407 West 42nd Street @ 9th Avenue, NYC, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    June 19
- Meeting Files, 4/6/00-6/19-00. (Box 15)
  - NSSB Committee Meetings & Executive Committee Meeting NSSB Boardroom, 1441 L Street NW Washington, D.C., 1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Institute (NYSNER) Presentation, LOB Hearing Room C, Albany, NY, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Dec 1, 11:30am
  - Advisory Council to School-to-Work, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Dec 1-3
  - NSSB Board Retreat, Holiday Inn, 625 first St., Alexandria, VA, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Dec 9-10